<Publish>
	<ModId Value="86944" />
	<DisplayName Value="Demand Master Control" />
	<ShortDescription Value="Fine-tune every parameters leading to stable demand control." />
	<LongDescription>
# Demand Master Control

Demand Master Control gives the player full control over how the city grows by allowing them to tweak various demand-related factors, such as employment rates, residential occupancy, tax effects, and commuter behavior. Whether you want a more realistic demand simulation or prefer a more customized experience, this mod provides the flexibility you need.

## Features
- **Happiness-Based Demand** – Adjust how citizen happiness influences residential, commercial, and industrial demand.
- **Workplace Availability** – Fine-tune how free job slots impact demand for different zones.
- **Tax &amp; Student Effects** – Modify how taxation and student population affect demand calculations.
- **Homelessness Impact** – Configure how homelessness affects residential demand.
- **Unoccupied Building Requirement** – Set the threshold for unoccupied residential properties before new demand kicks in.
- **Hotel &amp; Tourism Demand** – Customize how tourism and hotel room availability impact demand.
- **Industrial &amp; Extractor Demand** – Manage how demand for industry and raw material extraction is calculated.
- **Commuter Preferences** – Define the transportation preferences of citizens, commuters, and tourists.
- **Education-Based Citizen Spawning** – Adjust the probability of new citizens having different education levels.

## Configuration
- All options are fully adjustable via the Options panel.
- All options can be reset to vanilla using one click.

## Compatibility
- Works with existing saves.
- May conflict with any future mods that alter core demand calculations.
- No conflict with legacy infinite demand mods or "Super Fast Building And Leveling".
- Automatically disables conflicting settings when "Realistic Trips" is active.
	</LongDescription>
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshot01.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Screenshot02.png" />
	<Tag Value="Code Mod" />
	<ForumLink Value="" />
	<ModVersion Value="2.0.2" />
	<GameVersion Value="1.2.*" />
	<Dependency Id="" />
	<ChangeLog>
- Recompiled for 1.2.5f1.
	</ChangeLog>
	<ExternalLink Type="discord" Url="https://discord.com/channels/1024242828114673724/1270630977483444265" />
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/qstar-inc/cities2-DemandMasterControl" />
	<ExternalLink Type="buymeacoffee" Url="https://buymeacoffee.com/starq" />
</Publish>
